iOS Developer JOHN LIMA

 \checkmark

thejohnlima@icloud.com

+55 11
943064948

residente de la companya della companya della companya de la companya de la companya della compa

https://linkedin.com/in/thejohnlima

೧ thejohnlima

EXPERIENCE

PagSeguro UOL

iOS Developer | since July 2018

Working with native applications using Swift

BRQ

iOS Developer | April 2017 - June 2018

Working with native applications using Swift and Objective-C

Magna Sistemas

iOS Developer | February 2016 - April 2017

Working with native applications using Swift

EDUCATION

Learning algorithms, software engineer, databases, software development in FMU, Sao Paulo, Brazil

Analysis and Systems Development | February 2014 - June 2018

Learning a lot of concepts about iOS development in Impacta, Sao Paulo, Brazil

iOS Developer | March 2013 - December 2014

SKILLS

Also proficient in web services integration, external frameworks, fastlane, grew up bilingual (Portuguese and English)

- Xcode
- Swift
- Obj-C

- git
- MVVM
- CI

- cocoapods
- SPM
- Tests

About me

I'm passionate about technology, science, developing things that improve people's lives and make the world a better place. I've been working with mobile development for iOS platform since 2014 with experience on all steps of iOS development, from the concept of the ideas until releasing the app on the store and following the results with analytics, tests and crashreports.